{
    "subject": "resource/Lotte_Stam-Beese",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "Bauhaus",
    "human_readable": "Lotte Stam-Beese attended Bauhaus.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9707269668579102,
            "question": "Was Lotte Stam-Beese a student at Bauhaus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547250866889954,
            "question": "Did Lotte Stam-Beese study at Bauhaus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7503516674041748,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution Lotte Stam-Beese attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6988472938537598,
            "question": "What type of school did Lotte Stam-Beese attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6768519282341003,
            "question": "Where did Lotte Stam-Beese attend school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5643005967140198,
            "question": "Who was a student at Bauhaus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5136262774467468,
            "question": "What institution is associated with Lotte Stam-Beese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4664986729621887,
            "question": "What is Bauhaus famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3321209251880646,
            "question": "Is Bauhaus a school of art and design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.039393678307533264,
            "question": "Name an institution known for design and architecture."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lotte Stam-Beese attended Bauhaus.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1564_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bauhaus a school of art and design?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1564_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bauhaus famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1564_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution is associated with Lotte Stam-Beese?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1564_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1564_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Lotte Stam-Beese attended Bauhaus\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention Lotte Stam-Beese's affiliation with the Bauhaus. Specifically, document \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1564/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt\" mentions that she \"enrolled at the Bauhaus Dessau and studied weaving under Gunta St\u00f6lzl.\" Another document, \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1564/re-ranker-msmarco/96.txt\", also confirms that Lotte Stam-Beese was the first female student to enrol for Hannes Meyer's neue baulehre course at the Bauhaus."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Lotte Stam-Beese studied at the Bauhaus in Dessau from 1926-1929,\" which supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}